♪ Is violence in movies
and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those
good old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man
who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a...
Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
ANNOUNCER (on TV):
And now our feature
presentation,
Lawrence of Arabia,
presented in its original
Ulta-Cinemascope
letterbox format.
(music theme plays)
LOIS:
Well, I can't see anything.
STEWIE:
Who's the rather attractive
girl on the camel?
BRIAN:
That's Peter O'Toole.
PETER:
You film buffs might enjoy this.
Both his first and last names
are slang for "penis."
We interrupt this program
to bring you exciting news.
Family Feud
will be coming to Quahog.
Auditions are being held
tomorrow at the Civic Center.
Family Feud's
coming to Quahog?
Peter, we
should try out.
A family can win
$5,000 on that show.
$5,000?
I could get that cave for the
front yard I've always wanted,
and then tell people
not to go in there.
(kids laughing)
Hey, you kids stay
out of that cave!
You don't know
what's in there!
(sighs)
Money well spent.
We're looking for fun,
interesting families
that viewers will
want to watch.
You folks have any
interesting stories?
Lois, tell him about
the whole stitches thing
when Chris was born.
Never mind, I'll tell it.
Lois was so wrecked,
they had to sew her up
and open up a new vagina
right next to the first one.
You know, kinda like
when they build a new bridge
next to the old bridge,
and you're like,
"Wow, I can't believe
I used to use the old one.
Looks so unsafe."
All right, enough
clowning around.
Let's talk turkey.
We want to play the Feud.
Well, you're in luck.
The other family we've chosen
has three daughters,
so we're picking you
because you have three sons.
But I'm not...
Shut up, Greg.
(Family Feud theme song
playing)
ANNOUNCER:
It's time for the Family Feud.
Introducing
the Callaghan Family.
Ready for action.
And the Griffin Family.
On your marks, let's start...
the Family Feud!
With the star of Family Feud...
Richard Dawson!
Thank you. Thank you very much.
Ah, you're lovely.
I haven't heard
that much applause
since Bob Crane premiered
his home movies in my closet.
(Peter laughs)
All right, let's play the Feud.
♪ ♪
(applause)
100 people surveyed,
top four answers on the board.
Here's the question:
Name something you find
in your bathroom.
(buzzer)
A sink.
Show us "sink!"
(bell rings)
Peter, three answers
on the board that can beat that.
Name something you find
in your bathroom.
Find in your bathroom.
Richard, I'm going to go
with "fetus in the toilet bowl."
Show us "fetus
in the toilet bowl!"
(bell rings, applause)
Play or pass?
We're going to play.
Oh, this must be
your lovely wife.
(chuckling):
Oh, uh-uh.
I've been waiting
for this for years.
(moaning)
Okay, Lois, name something
you find in your bathroom.
Okay, how about
"bathtub?"
(bell rings)
(all cheering)
Okay, name something you find
in your bathroom.
Um...
a razor blade
and a note?
(bell rings)
(all cheering)
♪ ♪
Name something you'd like
to receive as a gift.
Candy?
Show me "candy!"
(buzzer)
(audience sighs)
Wait. We're out?
But you said if I slept
with you...
All right, Griffins,
here's your chance
to win the game!
Name something you'd like
to receive as a gift.
Groceries!
Assorted lotions!
An Uzi!
A dead squirrel!
Money!
All right, good answer,
good answer!
Yeah, money!
Oh, very good!
Good answer!
There you go!
Well, Richard, my family seems
to think money's the way to go.
So I'm gonna go
with the flute
that Captain Picard played,
first in his imagination
and then in real life, in the
episode "The Inner Light"
from Star Trek:
The Next Generation.
What?! No, you idiot!
We said "money!"
Show me "Picard's flute!"
(bell rings)
(all cheering)
Peter, how did you...?
I was in the survey.
Can you believe it?
We're going to the bonus round!
♪ ♪
(applause)
Okay, Lois.
15 seconds on the clock.
Name something
you sit in.
A chair.
My own feces.
Name a popular fruit.
Orange.
Clay Aiken.
Something in your closet.
Shoes.
Scary monsters.
Your favorite holiday.
Christmas.
9/11.
Something you do
on the weekends.
Go to church.
Black guys.
(bell rings, applause)
All right,
"Something you sit in."
You said "chair."
Survey said...
(bell rings)
Wait a sec. I said "feces."
Where's my answer?
Oh, you're just going to pretend
I'm not here, huh?
Just like Robin Williams' agent
pretends he's still funny.
(rings)
Hello?
Hey, Phil, it's
Robin Williams.
(laughs)
That's hilarious!
I just wanted to make sure
the meeting is still on
for 2:30 tomorrow.
Otherwise I gotta go
to that Chinese dentist.
Get it? 2:30?
(laughs)
You son of a bitch, I had
a mouth full of coffee.
God, you are funny,
and that is real!
Okay, Peter,
Lois did great.
You only need one point
to win the $5,000.
20 seconds.
Name something
you sit in.
Chair.
(buzzer)
Try again.
Big chair.
(buzzer)
No, that's
the same thing.
Try again.
High chair.
That's still a chair.
Chair.
Say something
other than "chair."
What if I can't think
anything?
You can pass.
How do I pass?
Just say it.
Say what?
Say "pass."
Chair.
(buzzer)
Oh, I'm sorry.
Your time is up,
and you didn't score
enough points.
But thank you
for playing.
Whoa, what, that's it?
We lose?
I'm afraid so, but we enjoyed
having you here.
You son of a bitch,
what about my cave in the yard?
What about my cave
in the yard?!
Get your hands off me.
I served
in the fictitious military.
Peter! Oh, my God,
are you all right?
What happened?
Where am I?
Who are you?
I'm Lois.
Lois who?
Who the hell am I?
Uh-oh.
Mrs. Griffin, I'm afraid
your husband has amnesia.
Oh, my God,
is it permanent?
Well, there's no telling
for sure.
His memory could return
in days, weeks,
years, or never.
Or weeks.
Peter, I want you
to meet your family.
You're... my family?
That's right.
These are
your children.
Dad, I'm Chris.
I-I'm your son.
Never seen you before
in my life.
Wow, then I must
be invisible!
Hey, everybody, I'm invisible!
HERBERT:
Oh, no, you're not!
Hot diggity!
This is Meg,
your daughter.
D'oh!
No, Peter, that's not
your catchphrase.
Oh.
Sorry, I just don't
remember anything.
Dad, this is your baby
and your dog.
Ooh, he doesn't
remember us.
It's an opportunity to come up
with our own names.
I'm Tomax
and this is Xamot.
We're twins who can feel
eachther's pain.
Ow!
No, Brian,
I'm supposed
to say "ow!"
You ruin everything!
Ow.
All right, Peter, we're going
to try to jog your memory
with some old videotapes
of the family.
Boy, you got
a lot of tapes here.
I kinda want to watch
some of these instead.
Pretty Woman?
What's that?
It's just a movie
from the '80s.
Oh, my God, we gotta watch this.
Look what they're
saying about it.
"As funny as it is touching!
Gene Shalit."
"I stood up and cheered,
'Go, Julia, go!'
Joel Siegel."
"This movie made me laugh
so hard I had mild headaches.
"So I went to the doctor
and got myself checked out.
I'm currently awaiting results.
Gene Siskel."
Everyone seems to love this.
We gotta watch it!
We'll watch it
later, Peter.
I want to show you one
of the most special times
of your life and mine:
our honeymoon.
LOIS:
I think you've had enough,
Peter.
(slurring):
Oh, you don't know...
Get away. I-I know my
body better than you!
Is that... us?
Yes, Peter.
You were so handsome
and it was such
a wonderful week.
Hey, buddy, I think
that girl likes me.
Of course she does.
She's your wife.
Do you like her?
I don't know.
(squeals, laughs)
(sighs)
You know, this isn't going
to be easy, you guys.
We're going to have
to re-teach your father
everything
he's forgotten.
Hey, have you heard
this awesome new song?
No!
♪ A well, a bird,
bird, bird ♪
♪ B-bird's the word ♪
♪ A well, a bird,
bird, bird ♪
♪ B-bird's the word,
a well, a...♪
This is called
a telephone, Peter.
You use it to talk to people
who aren't in the house.
There are others?
Yes, there are over six billion
people in the world.
Here, I'll show you.
We'll call my parents.
CARTER:
Hello?
Hello.
Who's this?
Carter. Who's this?
I don't know.
Do you have my OxyContin?
What?
Are you the guy?
I'm a guy.
I want my drugs.
What are drugs?
I don't think this is the call
I was expecting.
(hangs up)
Now, Peter, this is
your silverware.
You see, this
is your fork.
And this is a knife.
That's not a knife.
That's a knife.
This is also a knife.
Oh.
Well, I'll be
on m' way.
I want to see more of him,
and then suddenly none of him.
Forever.
(tires squealing, screeching)
All right, you know what?
This is not working.
If you're going
to learn to drive,
you're going to have
to practice first.
Here, play "Grand Theft
Auto" for eight hours,
and then we'll give
it another try.
(tires squealing)
So, you guys are
my best friends,
and this is where
we hang out?
That's right.
I'm Quagmire,
and this is Joe.
So, what do we do here?
Well, we usually come here,
you buy us drinks
and tell us what Loi''
nipples look like,
like you
always do.
Giggity-giggity.
Yeah, but first,
you usually go over there
and pull down
that blonde waitress's top.
(woman screams)
(loud slap)
She screamed,
so I had to slap her.
Oh, boy, oh, boy, oh, boy.
Get nude. Get nude.
Please get nude.
Peter, you don't
have to spy on me.
You're my husband.
Come on in.
Oh, boy, no fooling?
Oh, boy!
Wait a minute.
Something's happening
in my pants.
In the front this time.
That's all
right, Peter.
It just means
you're excited.
That's the way
it's supposed to be
between a husband
and wife.
It means you want
to make love.
But I forget how
Shh, shh, shh, shh.
That's okay.
I'll show you.
Just follow my lead.
♪ It feels like the first time ♪
♪ It feels like
the very first time... ♪
(moaning)
Wow! That was what
they call sex?
Yes, it was, Peter.
Can we do it again?
Huh? Huh? Can we?
Wow!
You're as excited as a porcupine
meeting a pineapple.
Hey, good-looking,
where have you been all my life?
(laughs)
Morning, nice people who
I still don't know your names
and who mean nothing to me.
Well, I certainly hope
that doesn't apply to me,
especially after
last night.
You got a point
there, hot stuff.
And if sex with the rest of you
is half as good
as it was with her,
then I think we're all gonna
get along just fine.
Yay!
Well, no, no, Peter, you can't
have sex with the kids.
Well, I wish you'd told him that
before he lost his memory.
(gasps)
It was a joke!
I was just
making a joke.
That's your
sense of humor?
I was just
kidding. God!
Meg, that's awful.
Geez, you open your mouth
for a joke once,
and that's what
you come up with?
That's messed
up, Meg.
I was just trying to be funny.
That wasn't funny.
That was just dark.
Yeah, that's your father.
Oh, get out, Meg!
Get out of the kitchen!
Go on! Get out!
Out! Out! Out!
Out of the kitchen! Go on!
Get out of here!
(laughs)
Oh, Peter,
there you are.
I've been waiting.
You ready
to have sex?
You bet.
Move over
so Tiffany and I have room.
What?! Who the
hell is she?
She's the woman
I'm gonna have sex with tonight.
Oh, and don't worry
about getting me pregnant.
I'm already pregnant.
Peter, what's the
matter with you?
You can't just have sex
with some random woman.
Why the hell not?
Because we're married.
Well, I'm sorry,
but I don't remember
marrying anybody.
Why the hell would I commit
to having sex with one person
for the rest of my life?
Because we love
each other.
That's part of
being a family.
It means being
responsible and faithful.
Well, that doesn't sound
very fun.
Well, if that's how you feel,
then-then we no longer
have a family.
Boy, I'm glad you said it.
But this is my house,
and I'm not going anywhere.
You don't have to.
I'm leaving, and I'm
taking the kids with me.
That's a beautiful necklace
you're wearing, Tiffany.
Thank you.
Is that what you do with your
Saved By the Bell money?
Mom, I don't want to live
in a tiny, gross apartment.
Well, I'm sorry, honey,
but we don't have a choice.
Your father doesn't
remember his life,
and he doesn't want us
to be a part of it,
so we've just got
to move on.
Oh, this is disgusting.
I shouldn't be here.
A baby doesn't belong
in the inner city
any more than a baby
belongs on a plane.
(crying)
Shh. It's gonna be okay.
Gonna be okay.
WOMAN (over P.A.):
Our in-flight movie this evening
is Hancock.
Waa! Waa!
(rock music plays loudly)
Peter, what the hell
is all this?
Well, I'm a bachelor,
so I invited a bunch
of people over,
and now I'm waiting
for them to leave.
That's what bachelors do.
Peter, I'm interested
in the redhead
with the wooden arms
and legs over there.
You think you
could introduce me?
That's a table,
Seamus.
Don't point at her.
Don't point.
She's looking.
Oh, great. Now
I got to go in.
Hey, I'm Seamus.
Peter, you left your family
for this?
Look, I don't know
what I was doing before,
but this is the way
man was meant to live.
I just know it.
Check it out.
(moaning)
Don't you miss your family?
What, that lady
and those kids?
I don't even remember 'em.
How could I miss them?
I almost don't want
to ask you out
because I know
you're gonna say no.
You want to go out?
No? Okay.
(to Jaws theme):
♪ Giggity ♪
♪ Gi-gi, gi-gi,
gi-gi, gi-gi ♪
gi-gi, gi-gi, gi-gi ♪
♪ Gi-gi, gi-gi ♪
♪ Gi-gi, gi-gi, gi-gi ♪
♪ Gi-gi, gi-gi, gi-gi,
giggity! ♪
Lois! Oh,
my gosh. Hi!
Oh, hi, Quagmire.
What a surprise.
I know, right?
Gosh, you know, I was just
picking up a couple hams
to take down to the shelter,
and here I run into you,
buying food to make
dinner for your husband.
No, actually, Glenn,
maybe you haven't heard,
but, uh, Peter and I
aren't together anymore.
What?! Why?!
Oh, it's a long story.
You don't want to hear about it.
Oh, shut your face.
I want to hear
all about it.
But listen, you know, I got
all this shopping to do,
so you want to stop by
tomorrow night?
I'll just whip
something up.
Well, sure.
You know,
that sounds nice, Glenn.
Holy smokes,
this is a sure thing.
Like the end
of a Mexican wedding.
(applause)
(cheering)
Aw, crap, we're out of milk.
I'm gonna run next door
to the airport and get some.
Hey, when you're over there,
can you get some rodent traps?
We got a giant mutant rat
living under the sink.
I'm just gonna hide
under the sink
till y'all go to sleep.
Then I'm gonna come out
and make my poops in your Kix.
Hey, Stewie,
is Lois back yet?
I've been trying
to get a hold of her.
She went to Quagmire's
for dinner.
What?!
Oh, that was a
delicious dinner, Glenn.
I didn't know
you could cook.
Well, when a fella's been alone
as long as I have,
he learns
to take care of himself.
Well, you're a
very sweet friend,
and you're so good to
listen to my troubles.
Oh, I could listen
for hours, Lois.
Phew! Boy, you know,
I don't know how a half a glass
of wine got me so lightheaded.
I better lie down.
You want me to
help you upstairs?
Oh, my God,
you are a saint!
No, I-I think I can make it
from here. I-I...
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
(both laughing)
Whoops!
Professor Klutz,
the doctor is in.
(laughs)
Oh, where is
this heading?
Oh, hiya, Brian.
All right, Peter,
now I know
your head is still
a blank slate,
but you got to listen
to me when I say...
Wait. Did you just
call me Brian?
Oh, yeah.
You've got
your memory back?
Uh-huh.
Happened yesterday on my way
back from the grocery store.
Hi, Peter.
Hey, you just snubbed me
in front of my own house.
I thought we'd come
to an understanding.
Look, fella, I don't know
who you are and I don't want to,
so why don't you just go back
to your crabgrass?
This happens to be
fresh Marathon Sod!
Oh, man, I just got
my memory back.
And as I recall,
I don't really care for you!
Wait a minute.
Who are you?
Hey, I know you!
What's your beef, stranger?
Well, if it isn't
my old nemesis!
I was just lucky he had
an odd number of objects.
Why the hell
didn't you tell anybody?
Well, I figured I could
enjoy the bachelor life
for a few more days
before getting Lois back.
Well, you may have waited
too long already.
Lois is on a date
with Quagmire,
and you've got to stop her
before something happens.
What?! Oh, my God! Where is she?
She's next door at his house.
And you better get there quick,
because with Quagmire,
sex is inevitable.
Like a fat guy ordering dessert
when everyone else wants
to leave.
So, does anyone
want dessert?
Ah, I couldn't
eat another bite.
No. I got to get home
for the sitter.
I'll have
the soufflГѓВ©.
That takes
45 minutes.
That's okay.
Oh, I can't believe
we're doing this,
but I got to say,
it feels kind of right.
I know, it's so
weird, right?
I mean, it's... I mean,
it's, like, fast.
I mean, it's fast, but it feels,
like, okay, you know?
I mean, like,
isn't that crazy?
It's like this adventure
that we're having together.
I know. That's exactly
how I feel.
I mean, it's a little strange,
but if Peter's never
coming back to me,
it's at least nice to know
I'm in the arms
of a trusted friend.
You... You trust me?
Uh-oh.
Wha...? Is something wrong?
I-I-I don't know.
I'll be right back.
(rhythmic whooshing)
Damn it!
Lois!
Peter?!
What-What are you doing here?
I got my memory back,
and I love you, Lois.
I want you and the kids back.
I want our old life back.
(Lois laughs)
I don't believe it!
Sweetheart, it's you!
You're back!
QUAGMIRE:
Oh! Damn it!
I'm back, Lois,
and I'm sorry.
I treated you so badly,
but I hope you know
it-it was only because
I wasn't myself.
I didn't just
lose my memory.
I lost my mind.
Clear!
(electrical buzzing)
Damn it!
Oh, my God, Peter,
I don't care!
I don't care.
I'm just overjoyed
to have you back!
Let's go home!
(electrical buzzing)
QUAGMIRE:
Damn it!
(buzzing)
Damn it.
Thank you for watching «Family Guy» on
www.FOX-fan.ru